hello my name is green and welcome back
to another episode of hermitcraft and
what what says donation and welcome to
the poorest hermit in the world iskall
iscal
what's going on here is it because you
lost all your diamonds or something
i like this is quite good actually
anyway the reason i'm here is actually
to take all this oh my goodness
sold all of it now i did actually change
the price from one emerald because
green don't math so well it turns out
this is a huge amount of emeralds
wow and all the extra oh my goodness
right that is a serious amount of
emeralds that i've got there eight
stacks in a bit and i've been absolutely
cleaned out now the reason i had to
change the price was because the impulse
actually sells emeralds for one diamond
for eight emeralds okay so if someone
had just went in here bought a load of
the emeralds they would have been able
to get eight stacks for a diamond
absolutely unreal so it still turns out
that one stack was half a diamond or one
diamond there's still green heads
everywhere keep finding my head
everywhere whoa where the heck did this
castle come from
now that we're emerald rich we are
protected a bit better
for when we lose our stuff i was even
thinking about being extra prepared by
going and spending this all on a new set
of gear
just so that i have one in storage in
case something in terrible happens
again
so that is nearly a stack of emerald
blocks and i've got my diamond block
still and this is yeah this is really
good this is good stuff
i saw a couple of comments the other day
on my last video now that i've opened my
demolition shop and i've got a bunch of
tnt i could use my new powers for good
in helping to clear out a lot of this
out okay
not always a door there part of me
thinks that this is not a safe idea at
all but the other half of me thinks this
could be really fun
if you look here there's a big portion
of netherrack that needs to be taken
care of
right up here but this means that we can
use the tnt to blow a huge amount of
this chunk without having to mine it
ourselves we just need to know exactly
where all of this stuff goes
this could go very very wrong well
oh wait where do i go where do i go
hey
not too bad
ah
it stopped you know what this could be a
really quick way of getting rid of
everything if only i'd thought ahead
fire in the hole fellas
off we go
yeah
[Music]
whoa
not bad not bad at all the lava might be
a bit of an issue that i didn't think of
but i think that this could be a quick
way of uh getting rid of stuff but it's
also
extraordinarily messy
i guess once it's actually all blown up
you have to carve it out by hand just
otherwise it will be a complete mess
but you can get rid of a huge amount of
blocks because i mean look at my
inventory it's 90 percent full of
netherrack
and
i just i just think that this could be a
really quick way as long as it's
controlled and thought out this could be
the way
whoa
where is this oh you
you
i've also seen that someone's left me a
little chest here that says i'm going to
need your help
oh no
i've only just given this away i didn't
think that this would be given back to
me
or they'd use it like so soon it's only
been a few days hasn't it
oh no
so this means that false
false needs my help with a prank
she's not online at the moment but when
she is i'll go and i'll go and speak to
her and see what she wants i think
perhaps while we're waiting
we could do a little bit of egging
so how have my little chickens been
doing
oh my goodness this is perfect are all
of these full yep these are filling up
pretty quickly
that's gonna keep us in decent supply
i still need to come up with an exit out
of here i've completely forgotten about
that anyway it's not really my problem
is it because it's the man in the
chicken costume
oh that was so swish
we're on the hunt for
justice where is everybody
is that a name
is there someone down there
what is
oh
well hello there
there can only be one poultry man
what is this
this is this is unacceptable what even
is this okay let's have a look treat
your chick you can adopt a lonely
chicken and provide it with a home it
deserves our poor chickens need
homeless chickens
so in short there are chickens that need
a home
what kind of hero would i be if i left
these poor chickens to be homeless
it turns out these adoption papers are
pretty pretty expensive
128 diamonds
oh my goodness and and what about this
one how much are you
i mean
i want to be a hero but
i'm not made of money poultry man
is poor
like
really poor all i've got is his eggs
all right this this chicken's gonna give
i need to be fed 64 quarts every cycle
of my life in return i will poop out
sand
so
this
this isn't this isn't homelessness this
isn't homelessness at all
this is chicken slavery i tells you i
have been bamboozled if you read these
books
they need they need to be paid quartz
and then they they poop out something
else this is this is unacceptable this
is ridiculous like
these these chickens
need freedom
that being said i am going to adopt
sally
um because i could always use the sand
so let's let's go and have a look at
what we need to do
so i need to head over to where these
chickens are being homed
and then i need to do something i'm not
sure i i don't know how i feel about
this these chickens are being used for
something which they shouldn't be
chickens are for laying eggs which are
used for throwing and that is all this
looks like the place someone's already
bought this one sally we're gonna be
best friends all right so basically i
need to make sally here a lovely little
coop that is going to keep her happy and
apparently her favorite biome is
the cherry blossom grove
so i need to feed her quartz which i've
already got a little bit of oh wow
it's going in
do i have to empty the litter tray or
something
it's actually going in that's pretty
cool
okay right now i just need to go and get
some resources and then we can start
but
this place
is for chickens but i don't see enough
chickens
[Laughter]
i knew i'd find someone eventually ren
you've just been poultry man oh no i'm
i'm almost i'm almost out of eggs what
kind of poultry man runs out of eggs
launch
where's he gone
i'm out of eggs so i've got a pretty
good idea of what i want to create here
and
it's basically a really tranquil like
zen garden type thing with a cherry
blossom tree as the main feature so what
i thought i might do
is create a big square
maybe like here
and create what is essentially
like a raked garden i'm not in shock
entirely sure how to
get this to look exactly the way i
picture it but it might work with a
little bit of tinkering with all of
these so what i've created is like this
weird garden thing that's like mostly
sand i'm really not sure what this is
but i have started with a cherry blossom
tree here now i haven't made one of
these in a really long time but i think
i remember how
it's all about the way that they lean
into or away from something and then the
branches
are
all about spreading quite far but on
thin like a thin layer so they all
spread out like this
and then adding a few fences in there as
well
hopefully i can get this right that
looks like a pretty decent configuration
maybe they need to be a bit wider but
i'm i'm i'm thinking this looks pretty
good
oh no i've jumped in with sally uh how
do i get out i also think we could do
with a couple of rocks like feature
rocks
they're not gonna go super high up but
just high enough to be
to look good i think now one thing with
trees i've put all these uh
pink leaves on but one thing with trees
is that they don't just sort of go out
like this you've got to remember to also
travel upwards just a little bit
especially when you get to the center
like there that way you can create a
feature piece right on the top although
i think i'm probably going to run out of
pink wool before i can finish this one
and then i can use the carpet here to
make it look like a few leaves have
fallen and then even mixing in just a
block there on the floor it yeah it
really works quite well i i mean i think
this looks pretty decent not bad for a
first attempt a few finishing touches
with a couple of flowers maybe a couple
of reeds and i think
this project is officially
finished
that's a i think that is a pretty good
little cherry blossom style thing i
think that's going to make sally very
happy indeed
and now to set sally free which okay
you're sally you're sally's friends okay
that's that's how this goes down and we
let them free i think i think that's
about it right that's that's all we
gotta do
now time to actually claim this
sally liberated by poultry man
this has gone pretty well i feel
actually i i'm i'm happy with this
so this one's mine and this one's cut i
got to admit the tree does not look as
good from up here at all i mean it looks
okay it's just not fantastic but when
you're actually here on the ground
it looks phenomenal because these trees
always look better from underneath so
at least it looks good from this angle
and looks like sally
which which one of you is sally
they all look happy so
i'm pretty sure that this is exactly
what you're supposed to do with this and
sally has been liberated by poultry man
all right well it's time to go back to
the base and take off the mask as we are
officially out of eggs ah false is now
online so i guess it's time to put on
my own head
and go and do the prank let's go and see
if we can find her shall we there you
are um so
you've left this in my base which means
you're calling upon
my services what's going on
i am indeed well i don't know if you've
heard yet because it's new news but um
yeah there's something at my base that
you might want to have a look at
what
involving me
uh
sort of yeah it looks very
possibly a little bit similar to what
you're holding there well okay come on
then let's go have a look let's go what
do you want about is it at your base
exactly uh-huh just go to the purple oh
oh
someone's pooped on your base no wait
well it wasn't me
what technically you have sort of
well i know someone's built me why did
they build me
i've got nothing to do with chickens
i yeah i don't know why that's it's a
bit random right
that is oh my goodness what a mess oh
what a real mess
it is quite a mess yeah this is this is
actually really impressive
what's he been eating
i don't know maybe he's had christmas
dinner early i think uh the chicken in a
green costume by rendog
oh my goodness i can put two and two
together you want to retaliate against
wren right for this well of course i've
got to right you can't poop on my base
without some sort of revenge exactly you
can't poop on your base at all what a
what an awful thing
uh okay so have you got any ideas for
what you want to do to ren i don't i was
hoping you might help me out a little
bit with that because i mean ren hasn't
really got much of a base at the moment
so it's a bit difficult to
know exactly where to prank him well let
me let me put my pranking face on there
we go um
[Laughter]
so ren doesn't really have a base base
right like not like us
nah not really he's just got that hole
which doesn't really do much but he has
got the grand central station has he got
any other builds that he has made
um
not not as big as that one no that's
that's pretty pretty central okay
let's let's go and take a look at it
cause i've not actually been exploring
in it too much maybe this is where we
prank because he spent a lot of time on
this a lot of time
he has pretty much the whole season has
been working at this this area actually
so yeah
he'll definitely notice if that's for
sure
well
we could
we yeah we could do something here maybe
we finished the track for him but we
send it on like a roller coaster around
this base
and then i'm thinking that it's not just
like an endless roller coaster maybe at
the end it it well it kills him oh well
of course i thought that was
obviously the ending i say what we do is
we build a giant wooden roller coaster
like you get in theme parks and then the
end
well he's gonna get on it right the
first thing he's gonna do is be like
what the heck he's going to jump on it
he's going to go for a ride and he's not
going to know where it ends up
and then that's the that's the
retaliation there that that that sounds
perfect yeah start here
and make our way around the whole thing
but we need to kind of think this
through all right so
let's go and get some materials and then
get started on this insane roller
coaster
okay so
i've got all the stuff here that we
might need i've got a bit of tnt
got rails galore oak planks this
should be enough to make what i think
we're going to make how's your redstone
ability by the way because mine is
non-existent uh mine's pretty much the
same yeah sadly
we may need to make it seem like this
actually ends
so what if we make like a decoy finish
point
so it's not actually connected
but
it looks like it finishes so he's like
lulled into a false sense of security
it's quite obviously a decoy at the
moment yeah oh yeah quite yeah quite
obviously this is not the way it works
um i think we need to take it all the
way up to the center of the tower maybe
we work it work it round like in a
spiral
yeah and then we make it go up and down
a fair amount maybe try and do a couple
of jumps now now false i i don't want to
i don't want you to get too far ahead of
yourself because i don't think this
works
oh
this could have been a very short
journey i don't know what this might
look like should i give it do you want
to give it a go i can give it a go yeah
let's explain i don't even know i've
never made a roller coaster before this
is all like theoretical for me
all right so you go up in a while
move down
nice the momentum's lost so much there
yeah i'll put a power rail down and then
you fall
and i missed it completely
that's kind of like like the jumping out
the window when everyone's holding a
blanket and this just completely missed
i i just removed these as well
yeah i didn't make i didn't i didn't go
very far
all right test two
you do lose a little bit of momentum but
it's okay you go super fast land here
and then
you're choking it again you just moved
it
[Laughter]
so we've been working on different parts
of the project right now i've gone and
i'm working like from the end and you're
working from the front so
yeah wow you've actually should i just
get in there and test it for now
i think so yeah and then i'll show you
what i'll show you what i've been
working on as well
all right here i go
up
okay so then it goes back down
we know all this bit
yeah
and then
get punched punched
and then we continue nice
and then ah punched again and oh
oh nice okay let me show you what i've
been doing so
i think that this should be a slow
and
painful end for rendog so
okay there's a this is the hole that
he's gonna go into
and hold on let me let me go down here
there's actually some string
that will activate when he gets to that
point and then that's gonna be wired up
to some dispensers which are going to
launch lava out and he's going to be
stuck down the bottom here which we're
going to encase in obsidian
so he just has to slowly watch as that
lava gets lower and lower and lower and
lower until it hits him here at the
bottom
yeah sounds good
yeah i got four buckets this is a test
once and a test once only kind of deal
all right all of my stuff is gone ready
captain oh yeah let me place it
yeah i'll send you to your death there
we go
oh you press it i can't press it
okay
three two one no i don't want to i don't
want to
don't worry i'll get i'll get it when it
passes by
it's actually going round yeah it's
still going around don't worry i'll i'll
just pick it up when it come passes by
mid mid transport god don't try this at
home there we go
all right
this is it for me
i'm gonna watch you come on bye this all
this this whole thing fails if ren
doesn't actually get on it you know if
he just if he just suspects us
that is true
you ready
oh no ah it still doesn't work no i'm
not
no you've got to go no don't
no
there's no need fuss there's no need
[Laughter]
don't make me fall down
there we go oh it was inevitable oh the
minecart's gone
this has failed so on so many levels and
you know what i'm actually stuck down
here because it's obsidian
yeah
i might need to chuck you some some
rockets or something right actually we
haven't got elite
have the six ender pearls
have fun with those oh great
you're gonna die on the way up ah that's
no no
i can make this
you live down there now no yeah no i'm
gonna live and die down here
there you go
so if i'm ren for the first time doing
this it should seem like a lot of fun
going around
going up
up up up up
jump
little jump and then this is when he's
like oh i'm going backwards look at me
i'm rendog
that's that's that's what that's what he
says
and then you go up and he's like oh look
it's even it's even got slime blocks
that's how that's what he's gonna say
and then
it's just going to chuck him straight
off the edge you hit this and you go
straight down and
activated
then there's some there's some signs
here ah
there's some signs here and then
i don't really have enough time to read
it but that's
i think there might be enough time to
get out if he's if he's got an axe on
him he could definitely escape
maybe oh i should put this slime box
back
this is it for me
that is it it's very slow death though
isn't it it's a very slow death
takes like an hour
oh boy
what i've written false is thank you for
riding the grand central station roller
coaster if you look above you you will
find your destination that gives him
enough time to read it and then look up
and see that and realize what's
happening exactly
and if he tries to break this obsidian
he's and if he breaks the slime he'll
realize he's he's uh yeah he's not going
anywhere now i i don't know about you
but i feel like this is just the the
skeleton i think we could definitely
decorate this a bit better with like
maybe some like fake log supports or
something it won't take long to put that
together yeah no that'll that'll make it
look a bit more legit like a roller
coaster but we can make it look like a
proper mickey mouse style roller coaster
that's held together by strings and a
chewing gum i think
we are officially finished we've added a
few support beams i mean they don't
actually look like they make that much
difference but
it kind of helps with the overall look
it makes it like we put more effort into
this than we did having said that we've
been recording this for like two and a
half hours now nearly three hours so it
has taken a while it's taken a really
long time
i'm not so sure about calling them
support beams they're not really much
for support
yeah they're just beams of some some
kind
we are
99 sure that this is going to work
yeah yeah
so it all finishes here and as long as
ren doesn't look too closely at it it
should all work
yeah i don't think he'll know what's
gonna happen at the end i think it'll be
a surprise yeah as long as he doesn't
look down that hole but even then if he
looks down the hole he will just see
some slime blocks and thinks oh it goes
underground so i think we're safe here
yeah i think so all right so i think
that's my prank uh taken care of though
i think we're now square that's the deal
done
yeah that is the deal thank you for
helping out yeah i mean fun the amount
of time it took us i can't imagine how
long this would have taken by yourself
yeah it would have been impossible all
right then i will see you later
that was an awful lot of fun actually i
really can't wait to see ren i hope that
he falls for it hopefully there's enough
decoys in there for it to work
and yeah it's been actually a really
good
prank i think so we've actually done a
lot today we went and adopted a chicken
as poultry man um wait no the the the uh
the the man in the chicken costume went
and
uh adopted a chicken mm-hmm
and we have done that prank as well i
tell you what i really need to sort out
this mess
look at this it's just shulker box after
shulker box there's just rubbish in 90
of them
i don't need most of this stuff it all
needs to get sorted i'm just so late
look at this
this is just going to end up being a
pile i'm going to look like a minecraft
hoarder or something i guess that we can
get rid of this
i really think i ought to get get
cracking on this maybe i can make a big
box or something like a big storage box
here
i don't really want to make
too many things in the other layers
because
realistically i don't have a working
elevator this room is dedicated to the
mumbo's mustache removal machine or the
mustachionator oh
looks like you're missing a piece of
your mustache there looks like i didn't
reset it exactly looks a bit it looks a
bit wonky actually i'll have to fix that
but up here i've got two more layers
that are completely empty this is empty
and this isn't wait i've got three
layers this is empty and this is empty i
was also thinking that what we could do
to the base
is make it look a bit more natural with
some leaves and stuff so i've grabbed a
bunch of leaves from these trees on this
random island and i'll kind of show you
what i'm talking about wow
mumbo's done some work here he explained
to me a while ago that he wanted to make
this look like digital and i guess
that's happened oh wait scar totally did
this didn't he's been waiting on scar
that looks awesome i i wonder if he
should have used kelp blocks because
then it may have looked like a uh
like a motherboard maybe he should try
that out but green we may need to chat
all right i'll go and go and find false
again maybe this uh leaf thing will have
to wait a while
is she back here at the
roller coaster
hello hello where are you here bye
up there hi uh what's
up um yeah i said we needed a chat right
um
yeah this
this prank yep
you know it's meant to be a retaliation
for the chicken thing yeah
uh we may have got the wrong person
what do you mean
apparently
iscol did that prank
but he signed it off as ren
i i'm not 100 sure basically
the sign said ischool and then
for some reason it says ren now as well
so
okay hold on i'm gonna hold on i'm
checking iskall's video
okay so iskall has definitely put his
name on it he took full ownership even
said it in the video
so something's amiss here me thinks
yeah something odd seems to have gone on
i don't know how that happens so we've
just spent three hours pranking the ron
a totally innocent person we have i feel
a little bit bad
i don't why i've got an idea
why don't we
blame iskal for this
and then
that's kind of a punishment right
yeah actually that'll that'll work
really well because then run will think
of ischool yeah maybe get him back
exactly and then we just pretend like we
had nothing to do with it
that sounds like a great plan
uh we just we gotta we gotta try and uh
write this the way is skyward i guess
uh-huh you know you wouldn't know
exactly how to do that right
i've done my best to sound exactly like
iskall
are you ready yeah go for it oh yeah hi
rendog is me ishkal your swedish friend
i have seen that your station is not
quite complete so
i finished it from you myself
please enjoy this fancy new system for
fast travel yeah ishko
sounds great yeah
sounds exactly like escort
believe it
yeah we're totally gonna get away with
this
i think so
oh no
we're so we're so busted
yeah we are we're a little bit
all right let's peace out okay are we
are we down for real this time
okay see you later bye
okay i think that's where we're gonna
leave it leave it
leave this episode this totally isn't
gonna backfire on me look at that it
looks so cool in the background alright
thank you very much for watching
everyone i hope you enjoyed this video
and good
bye